[
  {
    "_id": 86967581,
    "Level": "easy",
    "questionData": [
      {
        "question": "Question 1: Which city serves as the capital of France?",
        "options": ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
        "correctAnswer": "Paris"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 2: Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
        "options": ["Mars", "Venus", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
        "correctAnswer": "Mars"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 3: What's the largest mammal in the oceans?",
        "options": ["Elephant", "Blue Whale", "Giraffe", "Hippopotamus"],
        "correctAnswer": "Blue Whale"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 4: Which scientist developed the theory of relativity?",
        "options": [
          "Isaac Newton",
          "Albert Einstein",
          "Galileo Galilei",
          "Niels Bohr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Albert Einstein"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 5: Which gas do plants primarily use for photosynthesis?",
        "options": ["Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Hydrogen"],
        "correctAnswer": "Carbon Dioxide"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 6: What famous painting is known for its mysterious smile?",
        "options": [
          "Starry Night",
          "The Persistence of Memory",
          "The Scream",
          "Mona Lisa"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mona Lisa"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 7: Which scientist developed the theory of relativity?",
        "options": [
          "Isaac Newton",
          "Albert Einstein",
          "Galileo Galilei",
          "Niels Bohr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Albert Einstein"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 8: Which city serves as the capital of France?",
        "options": ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
        "correctAnswer": "Paris"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": 2895475645,
    "Level": "normal",
    "questionData": [
      {
        "question": "Question 1: Which city serves as the capital of France?",
        "options": ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
        "correctAnswer": "Paris"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 2: Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
        "options": ["Mars", "Venus", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
        "correctAnswer": "Mars"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 3: What's the largest mammal in the oceans?",
        "options": ["Elephant", "Blue Whale", "Giraffe", "Hippopotamus"],
        "correctAnswer": "Blue Whale"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 4: Which scientist developed the theory of relativity?",
        "options": [
          "Isaac Newton",
          "Albert Einstein",
          "Galileo Galilei",
          "Niels Bohr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Albert Einstein"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 5: Which gas do plants primarily use for photosynthesis?",
        "options": ["Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Hydrogen"],
        "correctAnswer": "Carbon Dioxide"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 6: What famous painting is known for its mysterious smile?",
        "options": [
          "Starry Night",
          "The Persistence of Memory",
          "The Scream",
          "Mona Lisa"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mona Lisa"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 7: Which scientist developed the theory of relativity?",
        "options": [
          "Isaac Newton",
          "Albert Einstein",
          "Galileo Galilei",
          "Niels Bohr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Albert Einstein"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 8: Which city serves as the capital of France?",
        "options": ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
        "correctAnswer": "Paris"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": 356876896,
    "Level": "hard",
    "questionData": [
      {
        "question": "Question 1: Which city serves as the capital of France?",
        "options": ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
        "correctAnswer": "Paris"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 2: Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
        "options": ["Mars", "Venus", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
        "correctAnswer": "Mars"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 3: What's the largest mammal in the oceans?",
        "options": ["Elephant", "Blue Whale", "Giraffe", "Hippopotamus"],
        "correctAnswer": "Blue Whale"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 4: Which scientist developed the theory of relativity?",
        "options": [
          "Isaac Newton",
          "Albert Einstein",
          "Galileo Galilei",
          "Niels Bohr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Albert Einstein"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 5: Which gas do plants primarily use for photosynthesis?",
        "options": ["Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Hydrogen"],
        "correctAnswer": "Carbon Dioxide"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 6: What famous painting is known for its mysterious smile?",
        "options": [
          "Starry Night",
          "The Persistence of Memory",
          "The Scream",
          "Mona Lisa"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mona Lisa"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 7: Which scientist developed the theory of relativity?",
        "options": [
          "Isaac Newton",
          "Albert Einstein",
          "Galileo Galilei",
          "Niels Bohr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Albert Einstein"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 8: Which city serves as the capital of France?",
        "options": ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
        "correctAnswer": "Paris"
      }
    ]
  }
]
